Contact

Plano, TX 323-423-2853 (Mobile) shaudisa@yahoo.ca

www.linkedin.com/in/shadisalighehdar-rn-78324081 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Leadership
Microsoft Office
Customer Service

Shadi Salighehdar, RN

Staff Registered Nurse at Medical City Healthcare (Formerly HCA North Texas)

Plano, Texas

Summary

Registered Nurse with excellent relational skills plus years of experience (CVICU, PCU, Spine & Ortho).

Recently, accepted an RN position at Medical City of Frisco. Thanks to Healthtrust Workforce Solutions providing me the opportunity of taking shifts at Medical City Frisco from ICU to ER, and Medsurg. Plus thanks to Inpatient Director letting me know of the positive comments of team members plus patients regarding my nursing care.

Experience

Medical City Healthcare (Formerly HCA North Texas) Staff Registered Nurse May 2019 - Present (1 year 3 months) Frisco, TX

HealthTrust Workforce Solutions Registered Nurse March 2019 - Present (1 year 5 months) DFW

Picking shifts as an RN with all HCA facilities around DFW area.

Baylor Scott & White Health
Registered Nurse
October 2017 - February 2019 (1 year 5 months)
Dallas/Fort Worth Area

 Performed as an RN taking care of CVICU patients, stroke and heart attack patients or patients

with intermediate medical or surgical problems in need for telemetry monitor.

• Used critical reasoning to develop, to implement and to evaluate care plan for Stroke and

Cardiac (Cardiovascular) patients.

• Member of Rapid Response Team and responded to Rapid Response Code.

- Certified in NIHSS (Stroke Assessment).
- Worked collaboratively with medical staff, and health care team to provide top quality care with

compassionate and professional manner.

- Participated and was a member of Falls/Safety committee.
- Assessed patient and family level of understanding to provide effective care and education.

Medical City Healthcare (Formerly HCA North Texas) Registered Nurse

February 2016 - October 2017 (1 year 9 months)

Plano, TX

- Worked as an RN at Cardiac Stepdown (Cardiac PCU) unit of Medical City of Plano.
- Performed all tasks with a patient-centered focus while seeking opportunities for

improvements of process and treatments.

- · Assisted patients with healing and recovery after surgery.
- Evaluated patient care needs, prioritized treatment and maintained patient flow.
- Educated patients prior to procedures and answer any and all questions for patients and family.
- Organized care of other interdisciplinary teams to patients.

Cedars-Sinai

Registered Nurse

March 2009 - June 2013 (4 years 4 months)

Los Angeles, CA

• Performed care to both pediatric and adult patients with spine disorders, back pain.

documented and reported assessments to Neurosurgeon/Physiatrist (ambulatory/outpatient).

- Evaluated patient care needs, prioritized treatments and maintained patient flow.
- Provided pre-and post-surgical (spine) education and care including wound care.
- Assisted physicians in minimally invasive procedures such as trigger point injection.
- Frequently performed as charge RN and involved in opiate intake research for the clinic.

- Planned strategies for team building and improving patient satisfaction.
- Trained several staff nurses to provide top-quality patient care.
- Coordinated with doctors and other multidisciplinary team members to develop care plans for patients.

Cross Country TravCorps Registered Nurse July 2008 - March 2009 (9 months)

Los Angeles, CA

 Worked as a travel RN at Orthopedic inpatient unit of Cedars Sinai from Jul 2008

to Nov 2008 (ambulatory/outpatient).

 Worked as a travel RN at Orthopedic Clinic of Cedars Sinai from Nov2008-Mar2009.

Sunnybrook

Registered Nurse

April 2007 - July 2008 (1 year 4 months)

Toronto, Canada

• Provided care for patient with heart failure, cardiac arrhythmia, heart attack, post cardiac

angiogram/angioplasty at the Coronary Care Unit.

- Performed pre-and postoperative care for patients who were going to cardiac procedures.
- Ability to function independently and as a part of the multidisciplinary team.
- Ability to handle a stressful environment in a positive manner.
- · Performed as a charged RN.

Hamilton Health Sciences

Registered Nurse

July 2003 - April 2007 (3 years 10 months)

Hamilton, Canada

 Provided care for patient with heart failure, cardiac arrhythmia, heart attack, post cardiac

angiogram/angioplasty at Cardiac PCU and Cardiac Care Unit.

- Performed pre-and postoperative care for patients who were going to cardiac procedures.
- Floated to Coronary Care and Intensive Care Unit.
- Assisted patients and doctors in bedside procedures.
- Performed preceptorship for the new graduated nurses.

Education

Grand Canyon University

Bachelor's degree in Nursing, will complete in October 2019, Registered Nurse \cdot (2018 - 2020)

George Brown College

Associate's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2001 - 2003)